final E10toppic1 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"He admitted not _____________ his colleagues well.","trueAnswer":"treating","falseAnswer1":"to treat","falseAnwser2":"treat","falseAnwer3":"treatstreats"},{"id":"2","question":"What will you do to earn _____________?","trueAnswer":"a living","falseAnswer1":"life    ","falseAnwser2":"a job","falseAnwer3":"a career"},{"id":"3","question":"The dance club ___________ Mai often goes to will be doing a performance this Christmas.","trueAnswer":"which","falseAnswer1":"when","falseAnwser2":"who","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"4","question":"He suggests that mothers _____________ are employed full-time will not be able to give their children enough care and attention.","trueAnswer":"Who","falseAnswer1":"Which","falseAnwser2":"whom    ","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"5","question":"She is skilled at _____________ cloth.","trueAnswer":"weaving","falseAnswer1":"giving  ","falseAnwser2":"doing","falseAnwer3":"carving"},{"id":"6","question":"This laptop is much more user-friendly, but it costs ___________ the other one.","trueAnswer":"twice as much as ","falseAnswer1":"so much as","falseAnwser2":"as many as ","falseAnwer3":"twice as many"},{"id":"7","question":"Lan couldn’t decide ___________ to work with on the project.","trueAnswer":"Who","falseAnswer1":"What","falseAnwser2":"How","falseAnwer3":"when"},{"id":"8","question":"All the best theatres and restaurants are ___________ within a few minutes walk of each other.","trueAnswer":"situated ","falseAnswer1":"laid","falseAnwser2":"seated","falseAnwer3":"stood"},{"id":"9","question":"Do you know who’s _____________ his pottery workshop?","trueAnswer":"taking over ","falseAnswer1":"bringing out","falseAnwser2":"passing down    ","falseAnwer3":"turning down"},{"id":"10","question":"Peter can just about get ____________ in German.","trueAnswer":"by","falseAnswer1":"Up","falseAnwser2":"Down","falseAnwer3":"out  "},{"id":"11","question":"Astronomy studies _______ and objects in it like the Moon and the Sun.","trueAnswer":"the universe","falseAnswer1":"the Moon","falseAnwser2":"the planet","falseAnwer3":"the Earth"},{"id":"12","question":"This city has one of the most ___________ underground rail networks in the world.","trueAnswer":"Efficient","falseAnswer1":"Fashionable","falseAnwser2":"Cosmopolitan","falseAnwer3":"fascinated"},{"id":"13","question":"Factories and offices should be built in ___________ areas only.","trueAnswer":"urban","falseAnswer1":"Rural","falseAnwser2":"Coastal","falseAnwer3":"Cultural"},{"id":"14","question":"Nam didn’t know ________ to find more information about the course.","trueAnswer":"where ","falseAnswer1":"What","falseAnwser2":"Why","falseAnwer3":"while"},{"id":"15","question":"In the future, men and women _____________ equal roles in society.","trueAnswer":"will play","falseAnswer1":"Play","falseAnwser2":"will be played","falseAnwer3":"are playing"},{"id":"16.","question":"I said that I remembered _____________ with him in a handicraft village, but he said I","trueAnswer":"Working","falseAnswer1":"was mistaken.","falseAnwser2":"to work","falseAnwer3":"work"},{"id":"17","question":" ___________ I was talking to my teacher, my friends were waiting outside the classroom.","trueAnswer":"While ","falseAnswer1":"In order that","falseAnwser2":"Although","falseAnwer3":"So that"},{"id":"18.","question":"Would you like to live in a modern house or a(n) ___________ cottage?","trueAnswer":"picturesque   ","falseAnswer1":"awful","falseAnwser2":"terrible","falseAnwer3":"bad"},{"id":"19","question":"I have _________ older brother and ____ younger sister.","trueAnswer":"an... a   ","falseAnswer1":"an... an","falseAnwser2":"a... a  ","falseAnwer3":"a... an"},{"id":"20","question":"The book ______ Amelie is reading now is about the Big Bang theory.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"whose","falseAnwser2":"who","falseAnwer3":"where"}]';
final E10toppic2 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"If you want to stay slim and healthy, you _________ reduce the amount of fast food you eat every day.","trueAnswer":"should    ","falseAnswer1":"May","falseAnwser2":"need","falseAnwer3":"would"},{"id":"2","question":"Sound symbolism means that we often ____________ the meaning of a word from its sound.","trueAnswer":"Guess","falseAnswer1":"judge","falseAnwser2":"imagine","falseAnwer3":"expect"},{"id":"3","question":"The station building used to be a high wooden _____ with a curved roof.","trueAnswer":"structure","falseAnswer1":"Facility","falseAnwser2":"Carriage","falseAnwer3":"Complex"},{"id":"4","question":" It`s a great experience to be sitting comfortably in a ___________ pulled by someone through the ancient streets.","trueAnswer":"Rickshaw","falseAnswer1":"Bicycle","falseAnwser2":"Car","falseAnwer3":"train"},{"id":"5", "question":"The garlic sausage is also sold pre-packed in _________.","trueAnswer":"Slices","falseAnswer1":"Stalks","falseAnwser2":"Sticks","falseAnwer3":"packets"},{"id":"6","question":"In winter, many Swedes travel to a country ___ there’s a lot of sunshine.","trueAnswer":"Where","falseAnswer1":"Which","falseAnwser2":"Who","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"7","question":"My grandfather is the ___________ oldest artisan in the village; Ngoc’s grandfather is the oldest.","trueAnswer":"Second","falseAnswer1":"First","falseAnwser2":"most ","falseAnwer3":"one"},{"id":"8","question":"A ___________ is a solid figure or object, made by carving or shaping wood, stone, clay, etc.","trueAnswer":"Sculpture","falseAnswer1":"Painting","falseAnwser2":"Medal","falseAnwer3":"picture"},{"id":"9","question":"All food products should carry a list of _________ on the packet.","trueAnswer":"ingredients","falseAnswer1":"Elements","falseAnwser2":"Materials","falseAnwer3":"Foods"},{"id":"10","question":"Beyond 2030 is a forum _____________ allows students to share their vision of the future.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"Who","falseAnwser2":"It","falseAnwer3":"and"},{"id":"11","question":"‘The cinnamon buns ___________ my mother makes are the best in the world!’ he said.","trueAnswer":"That","falseAnswer1":"When","falseAnwser2":"Whose","falseAnwer3":"0"},{"id":"12","question":"If you like, I can _____________ flowers on the cushion covers for you.","trueAnswer":"embroider","falseAnswer1":"Grow","falseAnwser2":"make    ","falseAnwer3":"knit"},{"id":"13","question":"___________ she’s young, she’s the most famous artisan in the village.","trueAnswer":"Although","falseAnswer1":"When","falseAnwser2":"Whereas","falseAnwer3":"In order to"},{"id":"14","question":"Today’s cities are ___________ than cities in previous times.","trueAnswer":"much larger   ","falseAnswer1":"lots larger","falseAnwser2":"as large","falseAnwer3":"the largest"},{"id":"15","question":" In this town, they _____________ all the frames in steel.","trueAnswer":"cast","falseAnswer1":"Make","falseAnwser2":"Have","falseAnwer3":"mould"},{"id":"16","question":"These red buttons are only used in case of _____________.","trueAnswer":"emergency ","falseAnswer1":"hurry","falseAnwser2":"rain","falseAnwer3":"sickness"},{"id":"17","question":"The new sports ___________ has six tennis courts.","trueAnswer":"Complex","falseAnswer1":"match   ","falseAnwser2":"medium","falseAnwer3":"game"},{"id":"18","question":"It is important to decide if promotion should be based on merit or ____.","trueAnswer":"seniority","falseAnswer1":"gender  ","falseAnwser2":"year","falseAnwer3":"weight"},{"id":"19","question":"He spoke a ____________ of French that we found hard to understand.","trueAnswer":"dialect   ","falseAnswer1":"slang ","falseAnwser2":"jargon  ","falseAnwer3":"language"},{"id":"20","question":"The paintings ____ Mr. Brown has in his house are worth around £100,000.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"Whose","falseAnwser2":"what    ","falseAnwer3":"whom"}]';
final E10toppic3 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Most tourist attractions in London charge an admission __________.","trueAnswer":"Fee","falseAnswer1":"Fare","falseAnwser2":"Ticket","falseAnwer3":"pay"},{"id":"2","question":"She spoke English with a(n) ____________ that I couldn’t understand.","trueAnswer":"accent    ","falseAnswer1":"stress  ","falseAnwser2":"intonation","falseAnwer3":"tone"},{"id":"3","question":"The flower was _____________ out of a single piece of valuable wood.","trueAnswer":"Carved","falseAnswer1":"Moulded","falseAnwser2":"Cast","falseAnwer3":"given"},{"id":"4","question":"I’m interested in doing ________ so I can stay at home in the evening.","trueAnswer":"a nine-to-five job","falseAnswer1":"night-shifts","falseAnwser2":"an evening course","falseAnwer3":"something adventurous"},{"id":"5","question":"I can have a conversation in Italian, but I’m a ____________ rusty.","trueAnswer":"Bit","falseAnswer1":"Lot","falseAnwser2":"Very","falseAnwer3":"too"},{"id":"6","question":"Travellers are advised to find an alternative _____ during road repairs.","trueAnswer":"Route","falseAnswer1":"Field","falseAnwser2":"Direction","falseAnwer3":"itinerary"},{"id":"7","question":"Louis Lassen, _____________ made and sold the first hamburger, was an American chef from Connecticut.","trueAnswer":"who","falseAnswer1":"which   ","falseAnwser2":"he","falseAnwer3":"whose    "},{"id":"8","question":"Will lessons ever ________ in places other than traditional classrooms?","trueAnswer":"be delivered","falseAnswer1":"Deliver","falseAnwser2":"Learnt","falseAnwer3":"be learning"},{"id":"9","question":"___________ they moved to the city five years ago, they still remember living in a small town.","trueAnswer":"Although","falseAnswer1":"Whereas","falseAnwser2":"While   ","falseAnwer3":"In order that"},{"id":"10","question":"All _____ must complete a visa form upon arrival at Singapore airport.","trueAnswer":"passengers","falseAnswer1":"Tourists","falseAnwser2":"Departures","falseAnwer3":"Customers"},{"id":"11","question":" Is English a(n) ____________ language in your country?","trueAnswer":"Official","falseAnswer1":"Mother","falseAnwser2":"living  ","falseAnwer3":"old"},{"id":"12","question":"_________ is visiting important and historic places in a city or an area as a tourist.","trueAnswer":"Sightseeing","falseAnswer1":"Travelling","falseAnwser2":"Wandering","falseAnwer3":"Sunbathing"},{"id":"13","question":"The hotel where we are __________ is quite luxurious.","trueAnswer":"staying","falseAnswer1":"Living","falseAnwser2":"Existing","falseAnwer3":"Remaining"},{"id":"14","question":"Make sure you __________ a hotel before you come to our island, especially in the summer.","trueAnswer":"Book","falseAnswer1":"Keep","falseAnwser2":"Put","falseAnwer3":"buy"},{"id":"15","question":"She ____________ up some Spanish when she was living in Mexico.","trueAnswer":"picked","falseAnswer1":"Took","falseAnwser2":"looked  ","falseAnwer3":"learnt"},{"id":"16","question":"Computers offer a much greater degree of ____________ in the way work can be organised.","trueAnswer":"Flexibility","falseAnswer1":"Flexible","falseAnwser2":"Flexibly","falseAnwer3":"inflexible"},{"id":"17","question":"Captain Cook discovered Australia on a __________ to the Pacific.","trueAnswer":"voyage","falseAnswer1":"Vacation","falseAnwser2":"Travel","falseAnwer3":"Cruise"},{"id":"18","question":"Louis is virtually bilingual ____________ Dutch and German.","trueAnswer":"In","falseAnswer1":"On","falseAnwser2":"For","falseAnwer3":"with"},{"id":"19","question":"It is hard for people of different ___________ to get along in an extended family.","trueAnswer":"Generations","falseAnswer1":"Genders","falseAnwser2":"blood   ","falseAnwer3":"families"},{"id":"20","question":"You can learn a lot about the local ________ by talking to local people.","trueAnswer":"Area","falseAnswer1":"Territory","falseAnwser2":"Land","falseAnwer3":"nation"}]';
final E10toppic4 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":" My boss promised _________ me a pay rise but he broke the promise.","trueAnswer":"to give","falseAnswer1":"Give","falseAnwser2":"giving  ","falseAnwer3":"gives"},{"id":"2","question":"I wish I could take ___________ where I can experience microgravity.","trueAnswer":"a parabolic flight","falseAnswer1":"an ocean cruise","falseAnwser2":"an express train","falseAnwer3":"flying course"},{"id":"3","question":"The Mona Lisa, _____________ is a painting by Leonardo da Vinci, has caused a lot of disputes.","trueAnswer":"Which","falseAnswer1":"Who","falseAnwser2":"It","falseAnwer3":"they"},{"id":"4","question":"Don’t forget ___________ your identity card with you to the interview.","trueAnswer":"to take","falseAnswer1":"taking  ","falseAnwser2":"take","falseAnwer3":"takes"},{"id":"5","question":"Some people say that the role of family _____________ to fit the development of society.","trueAnswer":"will change","falseAnswer1":"will be changed","falseAnwser2":"changes","falseAnwer3":"is changed"},{"id":"6","question":"The PGA, _____________ stands for Professional Golfers’ Association, organises a prestigious golf championship every year.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"who","falseAnwser2":"it","falseAnwer3":"whom"},{"id":"7","question":"There is general ___________ that Vietnamese students lack knowledge of the natural, or man-made, wonders of Viet Nam.","trueAnswer":"recognition ","falseAnswer1":"Accepting","falseAnwser2":"saying  ","falseAnwer3":"undertaking"},{"id":"8","question":" It is important to ___________ the wonders of the world so that future generations can see them with their own eyes.","trueAnswer":"preserve","falseAnswer1":"Destroy","falseAnwser2":"ignore  ","falseAnwer3":"remain"},{"id":"9.","question":"A spacewalk occurs ___________ an astronaut gets out of a vehicle while in space to do science experiments, or conduct repairs.","trueAnswer":"When","falseAnswer1":"Who","falseAnwser2":"What","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"10","question":"The good news is more money ____ on education in the next five years.","trueAnswer":"will be spent","falseAnswer1":"will spend","falseAnwser2":"spends  ","falseAnwer3":"is spent"},{"id":"11","question":"The students didn’t know ___________ to do to deal with the problem.","trueAnswer":"when  ","falseAnswer1":"where   ","falseAnwser2":"why","falseAnwer3":"what"},{"id":"12","question":"I’ve ___________ the product catalogue and decided to buy this table.","trueAnswer":"looked through","falseAnswer1":"found out","falseAnwser2":"closed down","falseAnwer3":"lived on"},{"id":"13","question":" She turned ___________ the new job in New York because she didn`t want to move.","trueAnswer":"down","falseAnswer1":"on ","falseAnwser2":"off","falseAnwer3":"up"},{"id":"14","question":"The doll has been _____________ out of clay.","trueAnswer":"moulded","falseAnswer1":"Embroidered","falseAnwser2":"Cast","falseAnwer3":"woven    "},{"id":"15","question":" I love going to this place ___________ it’s the quietest place in the city.","trueAnswer":"as","falseAnswer1":"so ","falseAnwser2":"though","falseAnwer3":"so that"},{"id":"16","question":"After I found all the information I needed, I ___________ the computer.","trueAnswer":"turned off","falseAnswer1":"switched on","falseAnwser2":" looked for","falseAnwer3":"put off"},{"id":"17","question":" I couldn’t sleep last night _____ the bar nearby played music so loudly.","trueAnswer":"because","falseAnswer1":"Although","falseAnwser2":"so that ","falseAnwer3":"while    "},{"id":"18","question":"The company tends ____________ people with higher qualifications.","trueAnswer":"to employ","falseAnswer1":"employ","falseAnwser2":"employing","falseAnwer3":"employes"},{"id":"19","question":"In _____________, students can study a work sector like applied business, design, health, or tourism.","trueAnswer":"vocational subjects","falseAnswer1":"academic subjects","falseAnwser2":"applied approach","falseAnwer3":"schedule"},{"id":"20","question":"This sports centre is so small that it cannot _____________ the demands of local residents.","trueAnswer":"keep up with  ","falseAnswer1":"face up to","falseAnwser2":"deal about","falseAnwer3":"set up"}]';
final E10toppic5 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"When I turned up, the town hall was already ___________ of teenagers.","trueAnswer":"Full","falseAnswer1":"Packed","falseAnwser2":"Crowded","falseAnwer3":"jammed"},{"id":"2","question":"I tried _____________ some essential skills before applying for that job.","trueAnswer":"to master","falseAnswer1":"master  ","falseAnwser2":"mastered","falseAnwer3":"mastering"},{"id":"3","question":"In the near future, a teacher will act more like a(n) _____________ than a giver of knowledge.","trueAnswer":"Facilitator","falseAnswer1":"Instructor","falseAnwser2":"Speaker","falseAnwer3":"listener"},{"id":"4","question":"I love it when we go to see plays, and try to ___________ when we get back home.","trueAnswer":"act them out  ","falseAnswer1":"Play","falseAnwser2":"role-play ","falseAnwer3":"act"},{"id":"5","question":" _____________ are the secondary education certificates awarded to students between the ages of 14 to 16.","trueAnswer":"GCSEs","falseAnswer1":"Academic subjects","falseAnwser2":"Careers","falseAnwer3":"SATs"},{"id":"6","question":"It’s good to have someone to ___ you when you are visiting a new place.","trueAnswer":"guide ","falseAnswer1":"Lead","falseAnwser2":"Take","falseAnwer3":"bring"},{"id":"7","question":"Japan is the ___________ developed country in the world.","trueAnswer":"second most   ","falseAnswer1":"most second ","falseAnwser2":"second in most","falseAnwer3":"two most"},{"id":"8","question":"He asked ___________ it was too early to apply for the course.","trueAnswer":"If","falseAnswer1":"For","falseAnwser2":"when    ","falseAnwer3":"that"},{"id":"9","question":"Is it true that you _____________ this woollen hat yourself?","trueAnswer":"Knitted","falseAnswer1":"Wove","falseAnwser2":"Did","falseAnwer3":"carved"},{"id":"10","question":"They keep changing the decoration of the shop _____________ they can attract more young people.","trueAnswer":"so that   ","falseAnswer1":"because","falseAnwser2":"although","falseAnwer3":"when"},{"id":"11","question":"The pagoda is in a beautiful ___________, close to the sea.","trueAnswer":"setting   ","falseAnswer1":"spaces  ","falseAnwser2":"tower   ","falseAnwer3":" set"},{"id":"12","question":"You don`t have to go to a supermarket for that. Just wait for a street ___________ to go past, and buy it.","trueAnswer":"vendor ","falseAnswer1":"person  ","falseAnwser2":"supplier","falseAnwer3":"purchaser"},{"id":"13","question":"The scenery is ___________ when viewed from the mountain top. It feels like your breath is being taken away.","trueAnswer":"Spectacular","falseAnswer1":"Nice","falseAnwser2":"Good","falseAnwer3":"peaceful"},{"id":"14","question":" It can be quite busy here during the tourist __________.","trueAnswer":"season    ","falseAnswer1":"phase   ","falseAnwser2":"period  ","falseAnwer3":"stage"},{"id":"15","question":"The local government is introducing tougher ___________ to preserve historical sites.","trueAnswer":"Measures","falseAnswer1":"Actions","falseAnwser2":"plans   ","falseAnwer3":"steps"},{"id":"16","question":"Production methods in the village are normally ___________ from ancestors to the younger generations.","trueAnswer":"passed down","falseAnswer1":"passed away  ","falseAnwser2":"passed out","falseAnwer3":"passed up"},{"id":"17","question":"Traditionally, an ‘English breakfast’ is a large cooked breakfast, usually _____ bacon and eggs, toast, baked beans, black pudding, and tea or offee.","trueAnswer":"consisting of ","falseAnswer1":"making of","falseAnwser2":"having      ","falseAnwer3":"existing of"},{"id":"18","question":"This is the space tourism service ___ is being advertised on our website.","trueAnswer":"That","falseAnswer1":"Who","falseAnwser2":"When","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"19","question":"___________ by the sea, the country has the advantage of having a large coastal area.","trueAnswer":"Located","falseAnswer1":"Situating","falseAnwser2":"Locating","falseAnwer3":"Stood"},{"id":"20","question":"____ people never seem to put on weight, while others are always on a diet.","trueAnswer":"Some","falseAnswer1":"All","falseAnwser2":"One","falseAnwer3":"Few"}]';
final E10toppic6 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Remember _____________ smartly when you attend an interview.","trueAnswer":"to dress","falseAnswer1":"Dress","falseAnwser2":"dressing","falseAnwer3":"dressed"},{"id":"2","question":"When you ___ your destination, your tour guide will meet you at the airport.","trueAnswer":"reach ","falseAnswer1":"Arrive","falseAnwser2":"get","falseAnwer3":"achieve"},{"id":"3","question":" More open discussions _______ online to help us reach a good decision.","trueAnswer":"will be conducted    ","falseAnswer1":"will conduct  ","falseAnwser2":"conducts     ","falseAnwer3":"conducted"},{"id":"4","question":"Would you mind _____________ me through to the manager, please?","trueAnswer":"putting   ","falseAnswer1":"to put  ","falseAnwser2":"put","falseAnwer3":"putes"},{"id":"5","question":"Minh is ___________ the most successful student in my class.","trueAnswer":"by far    ","falseAnswer1":"so long","falseAnwser2":"by how","falseAnwer3":"so now"},{"id":"6","question":"Ho Chi Minh City has been divided into twenty-four ___________ divisions since December 2003.","trueAnswer":"administrative  ","falseAnswer1":"Administer","falseAnwser2":"Administration","falseAnwer3":"administrator"},{"id":"7","question":"Lots of people choose to buy houses in the suburbs _______ they can avoid the noise and pollution in the city.","trueAnswer":"so that   ","falseAnswer1":"Although","falseAnwser2":"when    ","falseAnwer3":"so as"},{"id":"8","question":"A ___________ is a castle on high ground in or near a city, where people could go when the city was being attacked.","trueAnswer":"citadel","falseAnswer1":"Cathedral","falseAnwser2":"Monument","falseAnwer3":"centre   "},{"id":"9","question":"Working in a place full of hustle and bustle like this, I can`t help missing my tranquil and ___________ village.","trueAnswer":"Picturesque","falseAnswer1":"Modern","falseAnwser2":"Loud","falseAnwer3":"ugly"},{"id":"10","question":"Teachers provide a model for children to ____________.","trueAnswer":"imitate","falseAnswer1":"allow   ","falseAnwser2":" behave","falseAnwer3":"change"},{"id":"11","question":"He admitted not _____________ his colleagues well.","trueAnswer":"treating","falseAnswer1":"to treat","falseAnwser2":"treats","falseAnwer3":"treat"},{"id":"12","question":"What will you do to earn _____________?","trueAnswer":"a living","falseAnswer1":"life","falseAnwser2":"a job","falseAnwer3":"a career"},{"id":"13","question":"The dance club ___________ Mai often goes to will be doing a performance this Christmas.","trueAnswer":"which","falseAnswer1":"when","falseAnwser2":"who","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"14","question":" He suggests that mothers _____________ are employed full-time will not be able to give their children enough care and attention.","trueAnswer":"who","falseAnswer1":"which","falseAnwser2":"whom","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"15","question":"She is skilled at _____________ cloth.","trueAnswer":"weaving","falseAnswer1":"giving","falseAnwser2":"doing","falseAnwer3":"carving"},{"id":"16","question":"This laptop is much more user-friendly, but it costs ___________ the other one.","trueAnswer":"twice as much as","falseAnswer1":"so much as","falseAnwser2":"as many as","falseAnwer3":"twice as many"},{"id":"17","question":" Lan couldn’t decide ___________ to work with on the project.","trueAnswer":"who","falseAnswer1":"what","falseAnwser2":"how","falseAnwer3":"when"},{"id":"18","question":" All the best theatres and restaurants are ___________ within a few minutes` walk of each other.","trueAnswer":"situated","falseAnswer1":"laid","falseAnwser2":"seated","falseAnwer3":"stood"},{"id":"19","question":"Do you know who’s _____________ his pottery workshop?","trueAnswer":"taking over","falseAnswer1":"bringing out","falseAnwser2":"passing down","falseAnwer3":"turning down"},{"id":"20","question":"Peter can just about get ____________ in German.","trueAnswer":"by","falseAnswer1":"up","falseAnwser2":"down","falseAnwer3":"out"}]';
final E10toppic7 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Astronomy studies _______ and objects in it like the Moon and the Sun.","trueAnswer":"the universe","falseAnswer1":"the Moon","falseAnwser2":"the planet","falseAnwer3":"the Earth"},{"id":"2","question":"This city has one of the most ___________ underground rail networks in the world.","trueAnswer":"efficient","falseAnswer1":"fashionable","falseAnwser2":"cosmopolitan","falseAnwer3":"fascinated"},{"id":"3","question":"Factories and offices should be built in ___________ areas only.","trueAnswer":"urban","falseAnswer1":"rural","falseAnwser2":"coastal","falseAnwer3":"cultural"},{"id":"4","question":"Nam didn’t know ________ to find more information about the course.","trueAnswer":"where","falseAnswer1":"what","falseAnwser2":"why","falseAnwer3":"while"},{"id":"5","question":"In the future, men and women _____________ equal roles in society.","trueAnswer":"will play","falseAnswer1":"play","falseAnwser2":"will be played","falseAnwer3":"are playing"},{"id":"6","question":"I said that I remembered _____________ with him in a handicraft village, but he said I was mistaken.","trueAnswer":"working","falseAnswer1":"to work","falseAnwser2":"work","falseAnwer3":"works"},{"id":"7","question":"___________ I was talking to my teacher, my friends were waiting outside the classroom.","trueAnswer":"While","falseAnswer1":"In order that","falseAnwser2":"Although","falseAnwer3":"So that"},{"id":"8","question":"Would you like to live in a modern house or a(n) ___________ cottage?","trueAnswer":"awful","falseAnswer1":"picturesque","falseAnwser2":"terrible","falseAnwer3":"bad"},{"id":"9","question":"I have _________ older brother and ____ younger sister.","trueAnswer":"an... a","falseAnswer1":"an... an","falseAnwser2":"a... a","falseAnwer3":"a... an"},{"id":"10","question":"The book ______ Amelie is reading now is about the Big Bang theory.","trueAnswer":"which","falseAnswer1":"who","falseAnwser2":" where","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"11","question":"If you want to stay slim and healthy, you _________ reduce the amount of fast food you eat every day.","trueAnswer":"should","falseAnswer1":"may","falseAnwser2":"need","falseAnwer3":"would"},{"id":"12","question":"Sound symbolism means that we often ____________ the meaning of a word from its sound.","trueAnswer":"guess","falseAnswer1":"judge","falseAnwser2":"imagine","falseAnwer3":"expect"},{"id":"13","question":"The station building used to be a high wooden _____ with a curved roof.","trueAnswer":"structure","falseAnswer1":"facility","falseAnwser2":"carriage","falseAnwer3":"complex"},{"id":"14","question":" It`s a great experience to be sitting comfortably in a ___________ pulled by someone through the ancient streets.","trueAnswer":"rickshaw","falseAnswer1":"bicycle","falseAnwser2":"car","falseAnwer3":"train"},{"id":"15","question":" The garlic sausage is also sold pre-packed in _________.","trueAnswer":"slices","falseAnswer1":"stalks","falseAnwser2":"sticks","falseAnwer3":"packets"},{"id":"16","question":"In winter, many Swedes travel to a country ___ there’s a lot of sunshine.","trueAnswer":"where","falseAnswer1":"which","falseAnwser2":"who","falseAnwer3":"whose"},{"id":"17","question":" My grandfather is the ___________ oldest artisan in the village; Ngoc’s grandfather is the oldest.","trueAnswer":"second","falseAnswer1":"first","falseAnwser2":"most","falseAnwer3":"one"},{"id":"18","question":"A ___________ is a solid figure or object, made by carving or shaping wood, stone, clay, etc.","trueAnswer":"painting","falseAnswer1":"sculpture","falseAnwser2":"medai","falseAnwer3":"picture"},{"id":"19","question":" All food products should carry a list of _________ on the packet.","trueAnswer":"ingredients","falseAnswer1":"elements","falseAnwser2":"materials","falseAnwer3":"foods"},{"id":"20","question":" Beyond 2030 is a forum _____________ allows students to share their vision of the future.","trueAnswer":"which","falseAnswer1":"who","falseAnwser2":"it","falseAnwer3":"and"}]';
final E10toppic8 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"My house _________in 1986. ","trueAnswer":"was built","falseAnswer1":"is built    ","falseAnwser2":"was building    ","falseAnwer3":"has been built"},{"id":"2","question":"The doctor _________me not to stay up too late at night. ","trueAnswer":"Advised","falseAnswer1":"Suggested","falseAnwser2":"Insisted","falseAnwer3":"forced   "},{"id":"3","question":"Tomorrow we`ll go to Noi Bai Airport to meet Maryam, _________comes from Malaysia.","trueAnswer":"Who","falseAnswer1":"Whom","falseAnwser2":"whose   ","falseAnwer3":"that"},{"id":"4","question":"His house looks very large and beautiful. It is _________house.","trueAnswer":"a seven-room","falseAnswer1":"a seven-rooms","falseAnwser2":"seven room","falseAnwer3":"seven rooms"},{"id":"5","question":" If you get up early, you _________late.","trueAnswer":"won`t be ","falseAnswer1":"weren`t","falseAnwser2":"wouldn`t be","falseAnwer3":"aren`t   "},{"id":"6","question":"It`s very hot today. I wish I _________on the beach now.","trueAnswer":"Were","falseAnswer1":"Am","falseAnwser2":"Was","falseAnwer3":"had been"},{"id":"7","question":"When he lived in the city, he _________to the theater twice a week.","trueAnswer":"used to go","falseAnswer1":"uses to go","falseAnwser2":"has gone","falseAnwer3":"was going"},{"id":"8","question":"My father asked us _________too much time playing computer games.","trueAnswer":"not to spend","falseAnswer1":"not to spending","falseAnwser2":"did not spend","falseAnwer3":"to not spent"},{"id":"9","question":"Hoai can not remember the name of the restaurant _________she ate her favorite roasted duck. ","trueAnswer":"where ","falseAnswer1":"which   ","falseAnwser2":"whose   ","falseAnwer3":"whom "},{"id":"10","question":"If I were a flower, I _________a sunflower.","trueAnswer":"would be ","falseAnswer1":"was ","falseAnwser2":"were","falseAnwer3":"will be  "},{"id":"11","question":"Nobody went to the party, _________?","trueAnswer":"did they","falseAnswer1":"does he","falseAnwser2":"do they","falseAnwer3":"didn’t they"},{"id":"12","question":"It is nearly 3 months _________he visited his parents.","trueAnswer":"since ","falseAnswer1":"While","falseAnwser2":"during  ","falseAnwer3":"when"},{"id":"13","question":"_________population is another unpleasant result we have to solve.","trueAnswer":"Increased ","falseAnswer1":"Increasing","falseAnwser2":"The increase","falseAnwer3":"To increase"},{"id":"14","question":"If  we _________enough time, we’ll study this exercise more carefully.","trueAnswer":"have","falseAnswer1":"will have","falseAnwser2":"had","falseAnwer3":"would have"},{"id":"15","question":"Lan is very tired. ________, she has to finish her assignment before going to bed.","trueAnswer":"However ","falseAnswer1":"Although","falseAnwser2":"So","falseAnwer3":"Therefore"},{"id":"16","question":"What would you do, if you _________a UFO?","trueAnswer":"Saw","falseAnswer1":"See","falseAnwser2":"would see","falseAnwer3":"had seen"},{"id":"17","question":"I can’t understand the French visitors. I wish I ________French.    ","trueAnswer":"Knew","falseAnswer1":"will know","falseAnwser2":"know    ","falseAnwer3":"have known "},{"id":"18","question":"The church ________about 100 years ago.","trueAnswer":"was built","falseAnswer1":"is built    ","falseAnwser2":"will be built","falseAnwer3":"has been built "},{"id":"19","question":"People in Israel are going to celebrate their festival________is called Passover.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"whose   ","falseAnwser2":"who ","falseAnwer3":"where"},{"id":"20","question":" ________I was really tired , I couldn’t sleep.","trueAnswer":"Even though   ","falseAnswer1":"So  ","falseAnwser2":"Therefore","falseAnwer3":"Because of"}]';
final E10toppic9 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"I suggest ________some money for poor children.","trueAnswer":"raising ","falseAnswer1":"Raise","falseAnwser2":"to raise","falseAnwer3":"raised   "},{"id":"2","question":"She asked me if I _______a laptop computer the following day.","trueAnswer":"would buy ","falseAnswer1":"Buy","falseAnwser2":"will buy","falseAnwer3":"bought"},{"id":"3","question":" I ________telephone her if I knew her number.","trueAnswer":"would ","falseAnswer1":"have to","falseAnwser2":"will    ","falseAnwer3":"shall"},{"id":"4","question":" Honda motorbikes ________in Viet Nam.","trueAnswer":"are produced  ","falseAnswer1":"Produce","falseAnwser2":"will produce    ","falseAnwer3":"would be produced "},{"id":"5","question":" We have learnt English ________2001.   ","trueAnswer":"Since","falseAnswer1":"For","falseAnwser2":"In","falseAnwer3":"during"},{"id":"6","question":"We ________already _______Huong Pagoda. ","trueAnswer":"have…seen","falseAnswer1":"were…seeing ","falseAnwser2":"are…seeing","falseAnwer3":"will…see"},{"id":"7","question":"All the houses in the area ________immediately.","trueAnswer":"have to be rebuilt","falseAnswer1":"has to rebuilt","falseAnwser2":"had to rebuild","falseAnwer3":"have to rebuild"},{"id":"8","question":"If he ________soon, he might miss the train.","trueAnswer":"doesn’t come  ","falseAnswer1":"isn’t coming","falseAnwser2":"won’t come","falseAnwer3":"didn’t come "},{"id":"9","question":" Mr. Long said that he ________in Ho Chi Minh City.","trueAnswer":"Lived","falseAnswer1":"is living","falseAnwser2":"has lived","falseAnwer3":"will live"},{"id":"10","question":"Your sister works in a foreign company, ________she?","trueAnswer":"doesn’t ","falseAnswer1":"isn’t   ","falseAnwser2":"didn’t  ","falseAnwer3":"wasn’t   "},{"id":"11","question":"They_________Ho Chi Minh City last summer.","trueAnswer":"visited ","falseAnswer1":"Visit","falseAnwser2":"will visit","falseAnwer3":"have visit"},{"id":"12","question":"He asked me if I_________to school by bicycle every day.","trueAnswer":"went","falseAnswer1":"am going","falseAnwser2":"go","falseAnwer3":"was going"},{"id":"13","question":"    _________Friday morning, there is a meeting between 11am and 1 pm.","trueAnswer":"On    ","falseAnswer1":"In","falseAnwser2":"For","falseAnwer3":"At"},{"id":"14","question":"The article was posted by Jimhello on Tuesday,_________?","trueAnswer":"wasn’t it","falseAnswer1":"didn’t it","falseAnwser2":"was it  ","falseAnwer3":"did it"},{"id":"15","question":"She was sick yesterday,_________she was absent from school.","trueAnswer":"so","falseAnswer1":"since   ","falseAnwser2":"because","falseAnwer3":"but"},{"id":"16","question":"You really saw a UFO, _________?","trueAnswer":"didn’t you","falseAnswer1":"aren’t you","falseAnwser2":"don’t you","falseAnwer3":"weren’t you"},{"id":"17","question":"If Mr. John_________rich, he would travel around the world.","trueAnswer":"were","falseAnswer1":"Is","falseAnwser2":"will be ","falseAnwer3":"was"},{"id":"18","question":"Lan_________the train if she_________in a hurry.","trueAnswer":"will miss/ is not","falseAnswer1":"misses/ is not  ","falseAnwser2":"misses/ is","falseAnwer3":"will miss/ does not"},{"id":"19","question":"The book_________is on the table belongs to my brother.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"where   ","falseAnwser2":"whose   ","falseAnwer3":"who"},{"id":"20","question":"I didn’t go to the party yesterday because _________.","trueAnswer":"I was sick","falseAnswer1":"I am sick","falseAnwser2":"I will be sick  ","falseAnwer3":"I would be sick"}]';
final E10toppic10 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":". _________it was so cold, he went out without an overcoat.","trueAnswer":"Although","falseAnswer1":"Since   ","falseAnwser2":"If","falseAnwer3":"Because"},{"id":"2","question":"Tom said that he_________in Leeds in England.","trueAnswer":"lived","falseAnswer1":"is living","falseAnwser2":"has lived","falseAnwer3":"were living"},{"id":"3","question":"He asked me_________.","trueAnswer":"what my phone number was","falseAnswer1":"what my phone number","falseAnwser2":"what my phone number were","falseAnwer3":"what was my phone number"},{"id":"4","question":"Don’t forget to buy me a dictionary,_________?","trueAnswer":"will you","falseAnswer1":"do you  ","falseAnwser2":"shall you","falseAnwer3":"don’t you"},{"id":"5","question":"  The examiner didn’t tell me_________I passed or not.","trueAnswer":"Whether","falseAnswer1":"How","falseAnwser2":"If","falseAnwer3":"why"},{"id":"6","question":"Have you ever met the man________Mary’s cousin?","trueAnswer":"who married   ","falseAnswer1":"who is married ","falseAnwser2":"whom married","falseAnwer3":"who was married "},{"id":"7","question":"They are living in a house that________in 1930.","trueAnswer":"was built","falseAnswer1":"is built    ","falseAnwser2":"built","falseAnwer3":"was building "},{"id":"8","question":"If the weather________worse, we won’t go to the beach.","trueAnswer":"Gets","falseAnswer1":"will get","falseAnwser2":"got","falseAnwer3":"would get"},{"id":"9","question":" I’m learning English ________I want to get a good job after school.","trueAnswer":"Because","falseAnswer1":"But","falseAnwser2":"So","falseAnwer3":"therefore"},{"id":"10","question":"She’d love to take part in the evening class. ________, she has to look after the baby in the evening.","trueAnswer":"However","falseAnswer1":"Therefore","falseAnwser2":"but ","falseAnwer3":"Although"},{"id":"11","question":" My sister is very fond________eating chocolate candy. ","trueAnswer":"of","falseAnswer1":"At","falseAnwser2":"about   ","falseAnwer3":"with"},{"id":"12","question":" Paul was________sad about his exam results that he didn’t smile all week.","trueAnswer":"so","falseAnswer1":"Such","falseAnwser2":"Enough","falseAnwer3":"Too"},{"id":"13","question":" I suggest________a short cut through the park. It’ll take much less time.","trueAnswer":"taking    ","falseAnswer1":"Take","falseAnwser2":"to take ","falseAnwer3":"took"},{"id":"14","question":"Why________go to the park for a change?  ","trueAnswer":"don’t we","falseAnswer1":"we don’t","falseAnwser2":"we should","falseAnwer3":"we should not"},{"id":"15","question":"My sister is very________of spiders.","trueAnswer":"terrified","falseAnswer1":"terror  ","falseAnwser2":"terrify ","falseAnwer3":"terrifying"},{"id":"16","question":"Ba wishes he________have a new bicycle.","trueAnswer":"could ","falseAnswer1":"May","falseAnwser2":"Will","falseAnwer3":"Can"},{"id":"17","question":"This pen, ________is made of gold, was given to me by my father on my 14th birthday.","trueAnswer":"which ","falseAnswer1":"that    ","falseAnwser2":"whose","falseAnwer3":"when"},{"id":"18","question":"The interviwer asked me why I ________learning English.","trueAnswer":"liked","falseAnswer1":"like    ","falseAnwser2":"will like","falseAnwer3":"would like"},{"id":"19","question":"Your father doesn’t work in that bank,________he?   ","trueAnswer":"does  ","falseAnswer1":"Is","falseAnwser2":"isn’t","falseAnwer3":"doesn’t  "},{"id":"20","question":"My father________for the car factory since 1995.","trueAnswer":"has worked","falseAnswer1":"Worked","falseAnwser2":"was working","falseAnwer3":"is working"}]';
